<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>Canadian Curriculum History Project</title>
	<subtitle>Reconciling Canada&#39;s Curriculum History</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/feed/" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/"/>
	<updated>2022-01-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Michael Demone</name>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>About</title>
		<link href="https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/about/"/>
		<updated>2022-01-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/about/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;background&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Background&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/about/#background&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project was conceived in 2021 and my participation in Hacking History (HIS496H1) gave me the opportunity to treat this idea as a serious study in Digital Humanities. Hacking History equipped with the foundational knowledge in technology, data, to begin to think, plan, and develop projects for Digital Humanities. The project is in an exploratory development phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;inspiration&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Inspiration&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/about/#inspiration&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For many Canadians, the concept of reconciliation is a matter of government policy. Fortunately, the movement towards reconciliation recieves ample news coverage and we can now see businesses and institutiions introduce ways to include indigenous lives into their work and operational cultures. These are important and necessary moves, but I wonder what the &#39;average&#39; Canadian can do, on a human level, to connect with thier own past and make connections with indigenous commmunities. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/img/belt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Friendship Belt Tehontatenentsonterontahkhwa&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;The Friendship Belt, or The Covenant Chain belt, represents one of the earliest treaties between the Crown and First Nations peoples and established the foundation for First Nations - Crown relationships for generations thereafter. The belt shows that the Crown is linked by a chain to the First Nations peoples of this land. The three links of the chain represent a covenant of friendship, good minds, and the peace which shall always remain between us. The covenant chain is made of silver symbolizing that the relationship will be polished from time to time to keep it from tarnishing. This was the basis of the Nation to Nation relationship between the British Crown and the First Nations who became their allies in the formation of early Canada. [Image attribution] (https://vitacollections.ca/sixnationsarchive/details.asp?ID=2687120).&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;statement-of-purpose&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Statement of Purpose&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/about/#statement-of-purpose&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As my mother and I began the painful process of sorting through my recently-deceased grandmother’s things, among the many silk scarves and countless photographs, we came across an photo album of black and white photographs of my grandmother’s summers in the Kawartha’s, a favourite haunt of my family. The album, a leather-bound with a colourful illustration of an Indigenous person in headdress adorns the cover, inside were many photographs of typical Canadian summer activities like canoeing, swimming, and relaxing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apart from the familial sentimentality, genealogical value, and vintage Canadiana this photo album provides, it also prompted me to think about the connection between the illustration on the cover and the contents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Canada now joining the exclusive club of countries who have committed genocide I wondered what is my responsibility as the ancestor of settlers and pioneers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I think of my grandparents and others, who didn’t know or didn’t ask or didn’t care to know, I think the greatest crime I can commit not following them by not asking or doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I began to reflect on news and findings, I wondered what the responsibility of citizens, of Canadian people, do we have. My thoughts turned to the idea of responsibility as a vital component. But how do we think about responsibility. How do we envision responsibility through the education system when information, narratives, histories, are denied to us. This is how I arrived at the idea for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/img/albumcover.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Kawartha Park photo album, circa 1943.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figcaption align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;I discovered this family photo album while I was helping my mother sort out my grandmother&#39;s posessions.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-has-been-completed-so-far&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What has been completed so far?&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/about/#what-has-been-completed-so-far&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is a list of activities and project tasks that have been completed or are in process:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducted cursory literature review
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connected with Indigenous Scholar Pia Russell, author of &lt;em&gt;Whose History? A Reconnaissance of British Columbia’s First Fifty Years of History Textbooks, 1871-1921&lt;/em&gt;. Pia has agreed to start a conversation with me to see how we can further work in this area.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connected with Heidi Bohaker, Indigenous Scholar and Digital Humanist. Professor Bohaker has agreed to meet with me to see how our interests align. 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drafted preliminary Project Plan
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expanded knowledge area to include a consideration of applied ethics
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connected with staff at OISE Library and have begun preliminary primary source material research 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developed conference/paper abstract
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Submitted applications to present my preliminary project ideas to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dhn.utoronto.ca/&quot;&gt;Critical Digital Humanities International Conference&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ethics.utoronto.ca/c4e-undergraduate-research-conference-2022/&quot;&gt;Centre for Ethics Undergraduate Research Conference 2022&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Project Proposal</title>
		<link href="https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/"/>
		<updated>2022-01-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;topic&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Topic&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#topic&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Canadian Curriculum History Project (CCHP) seeks to explore the curriculum history of key and sometimes controversial subjects in Canadian public school curriculum.
The first initiative of the CCHP will be to examine the curriculum history of Indigenous peoples. This will include reviewing, documenting, and categorizing the depictions and representations of Indigenous peoples, cultures, and events in Canadian public school curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Canadians begin to address and reconcile the past policies of their governments and institutions, it is critical to understand what role education played in disguising, distorting, omitting, and erasing historical events and patterns, including state and institutional crimes. This project will examine representation through this lense and connect and correlate government policy and programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;project-design&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Project Design&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#project-design&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;description-and-design&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Description and Design&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#description-and-design&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Tools and Methods&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Deliverables&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scanned pages of text books and course materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis of material&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Website archive of material and analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My Story visitor contribution tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Performance Measures&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Audience and Stakeholders&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Primary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tertiary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canadian public&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Historians&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other scholars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Policy makers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graduate school application panel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grants, scholarships, other financial supporters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publications: Peer-reviewed journals, popular media, DH publications and outlets, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this time I do not have the requirements to submit a successful Master&#39;s application, but I would like to begin work on this project through a Senior Thesis or Independant Study. This, of course, will require the sponsorship and support of a faculty member. I would like to work with Matt Price, my instructor for Hacking History (HIS496H1).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once approvals are obtained and project proposel completed, these support members will be approached to solicit their interest and/or support for the project. I will also connect with various history, government and indigenous organizations to build support for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference Letters: Three letters of reference are required for UofT&#39;s MA History program and can hopefully be gleaned from the team members above.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Resources and Funding&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Timeline&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Description and Justification&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-initiation&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;2. Initiation&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#2-initiation&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Building a Project Team&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this project to be successful, and to improve my chances of a submitting a successful MA application, I will need to build a team of support including advisors and Subject Matter Experts. I envision needing the following people:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project sponsor and advisor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curriculum history specialist (OISE)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education specialist (OISE)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indigenous history scholar (UofT)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canadian history scholar (UofT)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canadian political history scholar (UofT)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Canadian policy/legislative historian&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technology advisor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Other Stakeholders and Interested Parties&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Media:&lt;/strong&gt; As the project takes form, I envion an aggressive publicity component to build support and awareness not only for the project itself but for Digital Humanities. Various websites and publications should be contacted with a releases and a project brief. The project subject matter is timely and newsworthy so with proper planning and support, it should get some traction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-planning&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;3. Planning&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#3-planning&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Project Scope&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the finsihed version of this website, the User will naviagate to relevant material by using HTML form with select elements:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Select from the options below to navigate to your curriculum:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;form action=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/action_page.php&quot;&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;cars&quot;&gt;In which district did you attend school?&lt;/label&gt;
  &lt;select name=&quot;cars&quot; id=&quot;cars&quot;&gt;
  &lt;option value=&quot;Halton&quot;&gt;Halton&lt;/option&gt;  
    &lt;option value=&quot;Kawartha Pine Ridge&quot;&gt;Kawartha Pine Ridge&lt;/option&gt;
    &lt;option value=&quot;Simcoe County&quot;&gt;Simcoe County&lt;/option&gt;
    &lt;option value=&quot;York Region&quot;&gt;York Region&lt;/option&gt;
    &lt;option value=&quot;Toronto&quot;&gt;Toronto&lt;/option&gt;
  &lt;/select&gt;
  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;dates&amp;quot;&quot;&gt;In what year(s) did you attend school here?&lt;/label&gt;
  &lt;select name=&quot;dates&quot; id=&quot;dates&quot;&gt;
  &lt;option value=&quot;1950&#39;s&quot;&gt;1950&#39;s&lt;/option&gt;  
    &lt;option value=&quot;1960&#39;s&quot;&gt;1960&#39;s&lt;/option&gt;
    &lt;option value=&quot;1970&#39;s&quot;&gt;1970&#39;s&lt;/option&gt;
    &lt;option value=&quot;1980&#39;s&quot;&gt;1980&#39;s&lt;/option&gt;
    &lt;option value=&quot;1990&#39;s&quot;&gt;1990&#39;s&lt;/option&gt;
  &lt;/select&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Submit&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-execution&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;4. Execution&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#4-execution&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-closing&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;5. Closing&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#5-closing&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;academic-proposal&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Academic Proposal&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#academic-proposal&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;rationale&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Rationale&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#rationale&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;review&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Review&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#review&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;outline&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Outline&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#outline&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;personal-statement-rough-draft&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Personal Statement (Rough draft)&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#personal-statement-rough-draft&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As my mother and I began the painful process of sorting through my recently-deceased grandmother’s things, among the many silk scarves, countless photographs, and I came across an photo album of&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Canada now joins the exclusive club of counties who have committed genocide I wondered what is my responsibility as an the ancestor of settlers and pioneers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I think of my grandparents and others, who didn’t know or didn’t ask or didn’t care to know, I think the greatest crime I can commit not following them by not asking or doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I then began to think about how I came to learn about First Nations. I had tacky trinkets and toys like headdresses, tomahawks, model teepees and birchbark canoes. I vaguely remember OKa ( I was thirteen).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most of my life I have lived no more than 50 kilometres away from a reservation, but would mean not much more than a quick joke about cheap smokes or cheap gas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was not until my first year in university, when reading a peer-reviewed journal did I learn from an international observer that there west problems at home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course I had read some Chomsky in grade 11 media studies (and continue to read him) talking about the American institution, but didn’t turn that critical gaze towards Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These experiences led me to the idea of studying what we learned in school and how that may operate to indoctrinate citizens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have always believed that every Canadian, whether the families of pioneers or new Canadians to at least ask what responsibility do we have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, we can leave institutional measures to the government, but what about at a human level, a community level. What can Canadians do to foster closer more integrated relations with our indigenous peoples?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mighty glitchy, BeChcombers, mythologies in cub scouts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently learned of the silver cup of peace and Covenant. Is this something we can look to as those willing to listen and participate in creating a Canada that is aware and accepting of past and looking forward to a future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we move from awareness and acceptance, what might action look like? Can we leave to givenntbt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can leave reconciling to governments and politicians or we can create opportunities to make connections with other communities, learn from our history, work towards a more just future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About taking responsibility. We are citizens in a democratic society and ultimately have responsibility for actions of government.  So&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we almost weekly read about the discovery of new graves holding the remains of indigenous children, and as we, as a society begin to reconcile our colonial past, account for MMWIG, and watch as our governments and communities address the reconciliation process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I began to reflect on news and findings, I wondered what the responsability of citizens, of Canadian people, do we have. My thoughts turned to the idea of responsability as a vital component. But how do we think about ressponability. How do we envision responsability through the education system when information, narratives, histories, are denied to us. This is how I arrived at the idea for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;to-read&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;To read:&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#to-read&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How education works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How curriculum works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propaganda, indoctrination, socialization, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is the function/role of the nation-state?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;research-process&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Research Process&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#research-process&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research Area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formulating research aim, objectives and research questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting the literature review&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selecting data collection methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reaching conclusions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completing the research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;digital-projects-proposal-assessment-questions-ecds&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Digital Projects Proposal Assessment Questions (ECDS)&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/proposal/#digital-projects-proposal-assessment-questions-ecds&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the project of scholarly significance to relevant fields of inquiry?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will the project&#39;s content be enhanced through digital intervention, and if so, how?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the project within the scope of the ECDS mission and priorities?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the project achievable with the current staff and resources available to ECDS and the project proposer? If not, can we build a sustainable proof of concept and work with the proposer to pursue external funding for further development?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the project achievable given the project proposer&#39;s current research, teaching, and/or work load?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the project sustainable? Consider who will be maintaining the project after ECDS, where the project will be stored, the lifecycle of the project, and if it can be archived.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is the project predicated upon the ability to secure rights to copyrighted material, digitizing analog materials, partnering with other institutions, receiving external funding, or other contingencies?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Document Study</title>
		<link href="https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/Document%20study%20sample/"/>
		<updated>2022-01-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/Document%20study%20sample/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
th {
  text-align: left;
}
tr {
  border-bottom: 1px solid #ddd;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Title:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Canadian Stories Reader&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Year:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1970&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Genre/Subject:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Canadian/Social studies&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Material:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Textbook&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Grade level:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;9-12&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;District:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;York Region&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Province/Territory:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Ontario&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Publisher:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Peter Martin&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;preface&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Preface&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/Document%20study%20sample/#preface&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This image from a secondary school Canadian Studies textbook depicts a wigwam...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/img/wigwam.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Wigwam schoolbook illustration&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussion&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Discussion&lt;a class=&quot;tdbc-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/Document%20study%20sample/#discussion&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several types of quantitative and qualitative analysis will be employed for this project including content analysis, such as coding, discourse analysis, and interpretive analysis. The standard historical document analysis framework of identifying the purpose, message, and audience....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://cdn.knightlab.com/libs/timeline3/latest/embed/index.html?source=1PvcYDRdwoR-NM7lUlYzJAWV1kcKP1GZ-1F1qHdYScL4&amp;font=Default&amp;lang=en&amp;initial_zoom=2&amp;height=650&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;650&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Your story</title>
		<link href="https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/My%20Story/"/>
		<updated>2022-01-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://hackinghistory.github.io/hh-project-11ty-starter-kit/My%20Story/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;
&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
.collapsible {
  background-color: #777;
  color: white;
  cursor: pointer;
  padding: 18px;
  width: 100%;
  border: none;
  text-align: left;
  outline: none;
  font-size: 15px;
}
&lt;p&gt;.active, .collapsible:hover {
background-color: #555;
}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.content {
padding: 0 18px;
display: none;
overflow: hidden;
background-color: #f1f1f1;
}
.collapsible {
background-color: #777;
color: white;
cursor: pointer;
padding: 18px;
width: 100%;
border: none;
text-align: left;
outline: none;
font-size: 15px;
}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.active, .collapsible:hover {
background-color: #555;
}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;.content {
padding: 0 18px;
max-height: 0;
overflow: hidden;
transition: max-height 0.2s ease-out;
background-color: #f1f1f1;
}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;I would like to share:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;form&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;radio&quot; id=&quot;html&quot; name=&quot;fav_language&quot; value=&quot;A memory&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;html&quot;&gt;A memory&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;radio&quot; id=&quot;css&quot; name=&quot;fav_language&quot; value=&quot;A story&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;css&quot;&gt;A story&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;radio&quot; id=&quot;javascript&quot; name=&quot;fav_language&quot; value=&quot;Some thoughts&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;javascript&quot;&gt;Some thoughts&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;
 &lt;textarea name=&quot;message&quot; rows=&quot;10&quot; cols=&quot;50&quot;&gt;
&lt;/textarea&gt; 
&lt;form&gt;
&lt;label for=&quot;fname&quot;&gt;First name:&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; id=&quot;fname&quot; name=&quot;fname&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;lname&quot;&gt;Last name:&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; id=&quot;lname&quot; name=&quot;lname&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;input id=&quot;emailAddress&quot; type=&quot;email&quot; multiple=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;bt&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;emailAddress&quot;&gt;Email address:&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;/bt&gt;&lt;/form&gt;
 &lt;h4&gt;May we publish your contribution?&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;form&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;radio&quot; id=&quot;yes&quot; name=&quot;options&quot; value=&quot;Yes&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;yes&quot;&gt;Yes&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;input type=&quot;radio&quot; id=&quot;no&quot; name=&quot;options&quot; value=&quot;No&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;label for=&quot;no&quot;&gt;No&lt;/label&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/form&gt; 
&lt;script&gt;
var coll = document.getElementsByClassName(&quot;collapsible&quot;);
var i;

for (i = 0; i &lt; coll.length; i++) {
  coll[i].addEventListener(&quot;click&quot;, function() {
    this.classList.toggle(&quot;active&quot;);
    var content = this.nextElementSibling;
    if (content.style.display === &quot;block&quot;) {
      content.style.display = &quot;none&quot;;
    } else {
      content.style.display = &quot;block&quot;;
    }
  });
}
&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;</content>
	</entry>
</feed>